why we what we are gonna create it
together is better than the current
iteration of open source so open source
is amazing it needs to continue and we
need to find ways to make it viable more
viable it is but like improve upon it
open source to me is there are issues
with it
expecially it won't especially the
technology space the only place that
exists is that in order to use it to its
full capacity you need to be a tech
person so there's like this two-tiered
system where if you understand
technology can basically hack then you
get to use these open-source tools to
the best of the capacity and not pay so
like you get them for free or next to
free whereas the less tech you have the
more you have to pay to access these
tools and the less good they are because
you can't code them right like you can't
improve upon them yourself and there's
no way to improve upon them and there's
no way to kind of find if it does I
don't know it exists and therefore
doesn't exist therefore it's the
marketing piece is broken on that that
to be able to say what's not working and
what iterations we want to go back into
the current one to say right that what
an amazing feature from this one an
amazing feature from this one but I'm
not a tech person and I can't put them
together even though the sort the code
is available to me so the transparency
piece of open source means almost all of
our project I am sure or we're gonna
vote to the open source unless there's a
reason we look at and we decide that's
not a reason for this project right
there isn't enough good there we don't
make it open source just to make it open
source but open source is powerful so of
course you want it there's subpar
projects in open source like Mozilla is
open source and I used it I always
downloaded it until I found out that the
Mozilla people the employees working on
Mozilla use Chrome because it's faster
and that was a decade ago so it might
might have changed
by now but although people can make it
better the whole thing isn't necessarily
made better by the people making it
better they're kind of dissipating that
energy instead of bringing it back into
one instead of saying okay well can we
use just this tool in this tool this
tool yes I want those so give me that
you know if we can make the open source
code be like Lego blocks where I can
choose or all of the Lego blocks are
available this really complicated
structure but I only get to see what I
can see so that it's it's something
simple for me we can create in a way
that it starts out subpar and not able
to compete in the marketplace but
because our energy of making it better
is going back into the whole it makes it
much better than what's currently in the
marketplace done in secret in isolation
that what we are creating together is
more powerful than open source how it
currently is because we and if it isn't
it's not going to compete them let alone
the you know Facebook and Google we have
to find because it's like the system of
creation and what we are creating that's
different it happens to be technology
but we're not actually a technology
company and that's gonna be its own
video but this was a bit of why although
we will use open-source we aren't only
open-source there's something else here
that open-source doesn't offer